#19 LAST MAN STANDING
Last One Standing - Simple Plan
How many times
有多少次
Are you gonna try to shut me out
你试图将我挤出?
I told you once  told you twice
我告诉过你无数次
I ain't gonna turn back around
我不会放弃
You can say whatever
你可以随意
Try to mess with me
抹黑我
I don't care  I'm not scared
我不介意，也不在乎
You don't have to say your sorry
别再满怀同情地
Save your sympathy
假装说抱歉
With a friend like you
有你这样的朋友
I don't need an enemy
连敌人都不如
I would give you time
如果你值得我对付
If you were worth it
我会奉陪到底
But guess what
但是
You're not worth it
你不值得
Whoa-oh  whoa-oh
I'm always gonna be the last one standing
我会笑到最后
Whoa-oh  whoa-oh
'Cause I'm never gonna give up trying
因为我从未放弃过
And now I'm ready to go
我已经准备好了
I'm here  I'm waiting for you
等你放马过来
And I'm gonna be the last one standing
我会笑到最后
The last one standing
笑到最后
Did you think
你以为
That I would surrender easily
我会轻易放弃
Just like that
你以为
You were getting rid of me
你能摆脱我
Is that the way
你以为
You saw it all go down
事情就那样结束
I don't think
不会的
I don't think so
我不这么认为
There's not a word you can say
你说的话
I haven't heard before
我都一一记着
So give it up  give it up
你就放弃吧
Unless you want a little more
除非
You think you're pretty tough
你觉得你漂亮是吗
So let's throw down
那我们比比看
It's alright  I'm alright
没关系，我比得起
Whoa-oh  whoa-oh
I'm always gonna be the last one standing
我会笑到最后
Whoa-oh  whoa-oh
'Cause I'm never gonna give up trying
因为我从未放弃过
And now I'm ready to go
我已经准备好了
I'm here  I'm waiting for you
等你放马过来
And I'm gonna be the last one standing
我会笑到最后
I won't give up  I keep trying
我从未放弃过
(I'm always gonna be the last one standing)
我会笑到最后
It's not over  I keep fighting
还没有结束，我会奉陪到底
(I'm always gonna be the last one standing)
我会笑到最后
I won't give up  I keep trying
我从未放弃过
(I'm always gonna be the last one standing)
我会笑到最后
It's not over  I keep fighting
还没有结束，我会奉陪到底
I keep fighting
奉陪到底
Whoa-oh  whoa-oh
I'm always gonna be the last one standing
我会笑到最后
Whoa-oh  whoa-oh
'Cause I'm never gonna give up trying
因为我从未放弃过
And now I'm ready to go
我已经准备好了
I'm here  I'm waiting for you
等你放马过来
And I'm gonna be the last one standing
我会笑到最后
Whoa-oh  whoa-oh  the last one standing